{
    "cards": [
        {
            "front": "あ",
            "back": "a"
        },
        {
            "front": "い",
            "back": "i"
        },
        {
            "front": "う",
            "back": "u"
        },
        {
            "front": "え",
            "back": "e"
        },
        {
            "front": "お",
            "back": "o"
        },
        {
            "front": "か",
            "back": "ka"
        },
        {
            "front": "き",
            "back": "ki"
        },
        {
            "front": "く",
            "back": "ku"
        },
        {
            "front": "け",
            "back": "ke"
        },
        {
            "front": "こ",
            "back": "ko"
        },
        {
            "front": "さ",
            "back": "sa"
        },
        {
            "front": "し",
            "back": "shi"
        },
        {
            "front": "す",
            "back": "su"
        },
        {
            "front": "せ",
            "back": "se"
        },
        {
            "front": "そ",
            "back": "so"
        },
        {
            "front": "た",
            "back": "ta"
        },
        {
            "front": "ち",
            "back": "chi"
        },
        {
            "front": "つ",
            "back": "tsu"
        },
        {
            "front": "て",
            "back": "te"
        },
        {
            "front": "と",
            "back": "to"
        },
        {
            "front": "な",
            "back": "na"
        },
        {
            "front": "に",
            "back": "ni"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぬ",
            "back": "nu"
        },
        {
            "front": "ね",
            "back": "ne"
        },
        {
            "front": "の",
            "back": "no"
        },
        {
            "front": "は",
            "back": "ha"
        },
        {
            "front": "ひ",
            "back": "hi"
        },
        {
            "front": "ふ",
            "back": "fu"
        },
        {
            "front": "へ",
            "back": "he"
        },
        {
            "front": "ほ",
            "back": "ho"
        }
    ]
}